let questions=[  
{ numb :1 ,
question:"Social Network is",
answer:"All of the above",
options:[
"A way for students to share ideas.",
"Not email",
"Related to web 2.0",
"All of the above"
]
},
{ numb :2,
question:"What is a trackback",
answer:"A type of backline",
options:[
"A social site",
"A type of backline",
"A spam method",
"A method of getting fake visits to your site"
]
},
{ numb :3 ,
question:"A blog can be used to",
answer:"Communication your news to the world",
options:[
"Communication your news to the world",
"Just to send send e-mail to your friends",
"To type my homework at home",
"To burn my cd's"
]
},
{ numb : 4,
question:"Who invented the term web 2.0 ?",
answer:"Tim O'Relly",
options:[
"Bill Gates",
"Yahoo",
"Google",
"Tim O'Relly"
]
},
{ numb :5 ,
question:"What Web 2.0 tool is best for collaboration ?",
answer:"Blogs",
options:[
"Blogs",
"Wikis",
"podcasts",
"Glogs"
]
},
{ numb :6 ,
question:"Web 2.0 can best be described as a (n)",
answer:"Approach to the internet in which users share thoughts . Strategies and open forum such as blogs,wikis and podcasts",
options:[
"Software package developed by Microsoft and available at discount to teachers",
"Approach to the internet in which users share thoughts . Strategies and open forum such as blogs,wikis and podcasts",
"Variation of the internet created by Al Gore in 1996 ",
"Faster internet for big business"
]
},
{ numb : 7,
question:"Which among these is not a Web browser?",
answer:"www",
options:[
"www",
"Edge",
"opera",
"google"
]
},
{ numb : 8,
question:"When did the term web 2.0 become popular?",
answer:"2004",
options:[
"2004",
"1994",
"2008",
"1990"
]
},
{ numb :9 ,
question:"When did the term web 2.0 become popular?",
answer:"They get better as more people use it",
options:[
"They get better as more people use it",
"Multiple users schedule their time to use it one by one",
"They provide users with content rather than asking users to create it",
"Web 2.0 application refers to a new version of a web 1.0 application"
]
},
{ numb : 10,
question:"What is the key characteristic of web 2.0?",
answer:"Sharing & openess",
options:[
"Better design",
"Sharing & openess",
"Better sound",
"User generated content"
]
},
];